大好消息  我朋友的奶奶死了
Great news, you guys... my friend's grandma died.
那很好  PJ
That's nice, P.J.
你根本没听他在说什么吧  老爸
You didn't hear what he said, did you, dad?
很好  盖比
That's nice, Gabe.
PJ  一个老太太死掉了  怎么是好消息呢
P.J., how is it good news that an old lady died?
因为我可以买她的旧车了  所以就是好消息
It's good news because now I can buy her car.
他们只要价一千块呀
And they're only asking $1000,
也就是说老爸可以帮我一把买下来
Which dad will help me out with.
我不会帮你买的
No, I won't.
神奇啊  你是怎么就能只听到你想听到的呢
Amazing. How do you only hear what you want to hear?
喂  我跟你们老妈结婚都20年了
Hey, I've been married to your mother for 20 years.
这种就是求生本能
It's called survival.
拜托了  老爸  我自己存了700块
Come on, dad, I've saved up $700.
你只要给我那个
All yo have to do is give me...
总之是剩下的就好嘛
The rest.
不行不行  我是你爸
No no. I'm your dad.
但我可不是圣诞老人也不是提款机
I'm not Santa claus and I'm not a bank.
我说  您的架式看上去就是兼容两者呀
Well, you're built like both of them.
老爸  求你了
Dad, please please.
我真的很需要有自己的车呀
I really need my own car.
开着杀虫车去载女生们兜风
Driving girls around in the bug truck.
完全没效果啊
Just isn't working.
没错  那东西完全失效了  说的就是杀虫车
Yeah, that's what's not working... the bug truck.
儿子听好  很抱歉  但我是不会给你钱的
Look, P.J., I'm sorry, but I'm not gonna give you the money.
我看你这事儿是没好运气了
So I guess you're out of luck on this one.
算你狠  老爸
Way to go, dad.
你是把一个老妇人死亡这种事
You just took an old lady's death.
变成很悲伤的事情了
And turned it into something sad.
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late,and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
■
校订： line
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
■
后期： line  追忆似水年华
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记第一季第二十集
Good luck Charlie S01E20 Girl Bites Dog
好的  小查莉  这些叫做工具
Okay, Charlie. These are tools.
这个是螺丝起子  这个是榔头
This is a screwdriver. And this is a hammer.
现在只要你能放对你的卡片呢
And if you play your cards right,
这辈子就不需要用这些玩意儿啦
You'll never have to use either of them.
好啊
Hi.
好  我从打工店里给你带了些东西
Hi. I brought you something from work.
这是"葡萄来见你"
It's grape to see you.
我见你也很荣幸
It's great to see you too.
哎呀不是  "葡萄来见你"就是这款冰沙的名字
Oh no, "Grape to see you" Is the name of the smoothie.
哇  好没创意的名字
Wow, that is lame.
是我起的名啊
I came up with it.
太好喝了呀
And delicious.
你好啊  小查莉
Hey, Charlie.
对了  我妈妈马上就下班回家了
Oh, so my mom's gonna be home from work.
大概半小时吧  之后我们就可以开始学习了
In, like, half an hour, and then we can start studying.
咦  我们今天要学习吗  我没带课本来哎
Oh, we were gonna study? I didn't bring my books.
好极了
Perfect.
你在干啥呀  玩这些小工具吗
What're you doing? Playing with tools, huh?
哎哟
Ow.
查莉  你干什么呀
Charlie, what are you doing?
这位是斯宾塞  又不是盖比
That's Spencer, not Gabe.
哎哟哟  她还真打到我了
Ouch, she really got me.
哎呀  真对不起  她平时不这样的
Oh, I'm so sorry. That's not like her.
没关系  她不是故意的
It's okay. She didn't mean it.
对吧  小查莉
Right, Charlie?
我是不是你的好朋友好哥们呀
Who's your buddy? Who's your buddy?
哎哟  她咬了我
Ow! She bit me.
查莉你怎么啦
Charlie.
晕  还真痛唉
Man, this really hurts.
抱歉呀
I'm so sorry.
或许她觉得你看上去很可口
Maybe she thought you were yummy.
我看是也许你们该好好喂喂她吧
Maybe you guys should feed her.
我们有喂她啊  虽然我自己没喂过
We do feed her. I mean, I don't,
不过我猜总是有人喂的
But I assume somebody does.
我最好去处理一下伤口
I'd better go get this looked at.
好抱歉
I'm so sorry.
那个  也许我们下次再找时间一起不学习吧
Oh, maybe we could not study some other time.
看看再说吧
I'll call you.
那好吧
Okay.
查莉  你把我的男朋友给赶走啦
Charlie, you chased my boyfriend away.
你现在高兴了吧
Are you happy now?
你在做什么啊
What are you doing?
在找掉落的零钱呢
Looking for loose change.
我要到处搜集到300块大洋啊
Gotta scrounge up 300 bucks somehow.
那你现在集到多少了
How much do you have so far?
一分钱
A Penny.
一颗棋子儿
A checker.
大概是一粒葡萄
Possibly a grape?
不是呀
No.
要是我说
What if I said
我可以解决你的小烦恼呢
I could take care of your little problem?
你能去除我嘴里这怪味吗
You can get this taste out of my mouth?
不是  我说的是关于300块钱
No, I'm talking about the 300 bucks.
你怎么会有三百块呢
How do you have $300?
很简单  我每天让妈妈给我做午饭便当
Simple... every day I have mom make me lunch.
然后又跟老爸要午餐钱
And ask dad for lunch money.
这样就累积的很快啦
It adds up quick.
那你是要给我钱吗
So you'll give me the money?
我是要借你钱
I will loan you the money.
哎呀  你知道我是有信用的
Oh, you know I'm good for it.
至少嘿嘿  你知道我住哪的  对吧
Hey, you know where I live, right?
是啊  现在你要在这签字
Yeah, gonna need you to sign this.
这是啥
What is it?
只是一张简单的合约
Just a simple contract.
我从网上下载的
That I downloaded from the Internet.
你慢慢看呗
Feel free to look it over.
晕  这纸上字够多的
Whoa, a lot of words here.
只是标准程序那些
It's pretty standard.
上面就是说你要还给我钱的
It just says you'll pay me back some money.
还有其他一些东西
And some, you know, other stuff.
我看可以
Good enough for me.
行啦
Okay.
你把名字签在日期栏里了
You signed where it says "Date."
幸好我未雨绸缪
And thinking that might happen,
这是另一张复印件
Here's another copy.
然后查莉就咬了他一口  这孩子为啥要这样呢
And then Charlie bit him. Why would she do that?
他是不是穿的像个大糕饼呀
Was he dressed like a giant cookie?
是啊  艾薇
Yes, Ivy.
斯宾塞是穿的像个大糕饼来着
Spencer was dressed like a giant cookie.
我说正经的哪
I'm serious.
查莉以前从没这样做过  对谁都没有
Charlie's never done this before, like, with anyone.
那也许小查莉感觉到斯宾塞有哪里不对劲吧
Well, maybe Charlie senses there's something wrong with Spencer.
有句老话说
You know what they say...
小孩和狗是最能慧眼识人品的
Dogs and kids are the best judges of character.
是哦  可是斯宾塞哪里会有问题呢
Yeah, what could possibly be wrong with Spencer?
他又帅又聪明
He's good looking. He's smart.
还是橄榄球队的队长
He's Captain of the football team.
而且他很喜欢我
And he likes me.
但你真正了解他多少呢
But how much do you really know about him?
斯宾塞也许隐瞒了什么  每个人都有秘密
Spencer could be hiding something. Everybody has a secret.
是这样吗
Oh yeah?
那你的秘密是什么
What's your secret?
我热爱乡村音乐啊  你看  我说了吧
I love country music. There, I said it.
你才没有咧
You do not.
不信啊
Oh?
看好了
Check this out.
来了
Oh yeah.
来吧  跟我一起跳
Come on, do it with me.
你知道自己想跳的
You know you want to.
哎呀  管他的
Oh, what the heck.
向左
To the left.
向后
To the back.
踢腿
Kick it.
你有何感想啊  妈妈
What do you think, mom?
哇  这是
Wow, it's...
这是一辆车
It's a car.
你从哪儿弄来的
Where did you get it?
本来是我朋友的奶奶的车
It used to belong to my friend's grandma.
喔  她以后不开车了吗
Oh, did she stop driving?
不是  她是再也不呼吸了
No, breathing.
她那时正要去吃自助餐的路上
She was on her way to a buffet.
结果走了岔道去了天堂
And took a detour to heaven.
不是吧
Oh no.
幸运的是她当时正好停在路口
Luckily she was at a stop sign,
所以身体才没有任何损伤  我是说车身啦
So there was no body damage... to the car, I mean.
那就是说她是在这车上死的
Okay, so she passed away in here?
就在你坐的地方
Right where you're sitting.
昏  我要出去
And I'm out.
啊哈
Ahh.
啊哈  新车的新鲜气味啊
Ah, the new car smell.
搞不好是死掉的气味
Or is it death?
载我去游戏中心  快点儿
Take me to the arcade. Step on it.
你说啥呢
Excuse me?
游戏中心的意思就是充满欢乐和游戏的地方
Arcade... place for fun and games.
快点儿的意思就是让你加速开车
Step on it... to drive quickly.
我才不要载你去什么地方呢
I'm not taking you anywhere.
我看是某些人没有好好看他的合约吧
I guess somebody didn't read his contract,
那上面清楚表明了
Which clearly States.
你有义务开车载我
That you have to give me a ride.
在任何时间去任何我想去的地方
Whenever and wherever I want.
你小子耍我啊
You tricked me.
戴上这  我给你弄了顶很屌的帽子
Here, I brought you a cute little cap to wear.
让你给我当司机时戴着
While you're driving me around.
喂  斯宾塞
Hey, Spencer.
什么事啊
What's up?
我想问问我们今晚还见面吗
I just wanted to see if we were still on for tonight.
我妈有夜班  所以就只剩你和我在家哦
My mom's working, so it's just gonna be you and me.
那很好啊
That's great.
当然还有小查莉
And of course Charlie.
哎哟  等一下
Oh, wait a minute.
你说今晚吗  我完全忘了  我有事要做
Tonight? I totally forgot. I have a thing.
有事做吗  什么事啊
A thing? What kind of thing?
是家里的事儿  我推不掉的
It's a family thing. I can't get out of it.
真的吗  你确定
Oh really? Are you sure?
妹子  他是不会去啦
Honey, he's not coming.
现在给我去剁点水果放到搅碎机里去
Now chop me up something and put it in the blender.
呀  我记得你说今晚有事的
Hey, I thought you said you had a thing.
是啊  不过我想我要跟你谈谈
Yeah, but I think we need to talk.
那好吧  进来再说
Oh, okay. Come on in.
我看还是在外面说好了
I'd rather do this out here.
也行
Okay.
怎么了
What's going on?
泰迪  我觉得这事儿成不了
Teddy, I don't think this is working out.
什么事成不了啊
What's not working out?
我俩的事
Us.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你是要跟我分手吗
Are you breaking up with me?
是的
Yes.
为什么啊
Why?
都是因为她
Because of her.
斯宾塞  等等
Spencer, wait!
斯宾塞  斯宾塞
Spencer! Spencer!
还好是个梦
It was just a dream.
泰迪宝贝  我差点忘了
Oh, Teddy honey, I almost forgot.
今天想让你放学后照看一下查莉
I'm gonna need you to watch Charlie after school.
我要去看牙医
I have a dentist's appointment.
不行  我有别的计划不能看着查莉
No, I can't watch Charlie. I have plans.
我要去斯宾塞上班时给他个惊喜探班
I was gonna go surprise Spencer at work.
泰迪  我镶了个假牙在嘴巴里
Teddy, I've had a temporary crown.
自从我怀孕时就有了
Since I was pregnant.
是怀上你的时候
With you.
妈妈  妈妈  查莉想拆散我和斯宾塞啊
Mom, mom, mom, Charlie's been driving Spencer and I apart.
要是今天我不能去见他
And if I don't go see him today,
我俩的关系就摇摇欲坠了
Our entire relationship might be at stake.
噢喲  得了  你冷靜先
Whoa. Okay, calm down here.
我也曾经历过花季少女  我很了解你的心路
I was a teenager once. I know what you're going through.
所以我要把当年我遇到这种事时
And I'm gonna say to you exactly
我老妈说过的话  原封不动送给你
what my mom said to me in times like this...
忘掉算数
Get over it.
这太不公平啊
That's so unfair.
她回答说  "自己忍着去"
"Deal with it," She said to me.
你毁了我的生活
You're ruining my life.
我也这样对她说的
I said to her.
我现在是可以继续告诉你之后的谈话内容
Now I could give you the rest of the conversation,
不过还是省省事吧  反正你必须要照看她
But let's just cut to the chase... you're babysitting.
就算你想掐死我也没用
Strangling me is not gonna help.
老爸  老爸  老爸
Dad, dad, dad!
喂  喂
Hey! Hey!
老爸快救我
Help me, dad!
喂喂喂
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
你俩闹啥呢
What is going on?
那小子说现在我的车是他的了
He says he owns my car now.
你拒绝了载我去我想去的地方
You refused to take me where I wanted to go,
也就造成你对我们的合同违约了
Which means you're in violation of our contract.
什么合同啊
What contract?
给  您自己看吧
Here, read this for yourself.
哇  这纸上字真多
Whoa, a lot of words here.
条款写的很清楚的
It clearly States.
上面说如果PJ不载我去我想去的地方
That if P.J. Doesn't drive me wherever I want,
那老太太的车就是我的了
The old lady's car is mine.
PJ  你确实是签了字的
P.J., you did sign it.
老爸  这不公平  这小子骗了我
Dad, it isn't fair. He tricked me.
好吧好吧  行了  我知道了  这样吧
Okay okay, all right, all right, here we go.
真是为人父者不容易呀
The hard part about being a dad...
总要做出棘手的决定  对吧
Making the tough decisions, right?
那么我的决定就是
So my decision...
等等  你看看第5页第3段
Uh, check page five, third paragraph.
"此合约内容不受鲍伯·邓肯判决管束"
"This contract is not subject. R= arbitration by Bob Duncan."
咦
Huh.
没法子  PJ  我管不到这事了
Sorry, P.J., my hands are tied.
能让我至少小小教训他一下不
Can I at least hurt him a little?
不行
No.
演出开始了
Giddy-up.
大姐  你还真把西部乡村风格发挥到极致了
Boy, you've really embraced the whole country Western thing.
我从未感觉如此生机勃勃  哟
I've never felt so alive, y'all.
我就像感恩节后的火鸡那么兴高采烈
I'm happy as a Turkey the day after Thanksgiving,
因为它们没被杀了吃掉啊
'cause it didn't get killed and eaten...
哟
Y'all.
其实吧  真正的村里人
Yeah, real country people.
他们是不会在每句话后面都加一个哟字的
Don't say "Y'all" After every sentence.
我看你最好是让他们说个痛快
I think you let them say what they want.
如果你还想要人家帮你照看妹妹的话
When they're babysitting your sister.
那好吧  查莉在楼上睡觉
Right. So Charlie's upstairs taking a nap.
等她醒后  她可能会有点饿
And when she wakes up, she might be a little hungry.
别担心  搭档  我会给她整点吃的
Don't worry, partner. I'll rustle her up some grub.
那就行
Okay, well,
我最好是套马配鞍  溜达到商场去
I'd better hop in the saddle and mosey on down to the mall.
在斯宾塞下班前哟
Before Spencer's shift ends.
我说  只有我自己用这腔调才有意思
Yeah, it's only cool when I do it.
你发啥疯呢
What's wrong with you?
你想要那车是吧  给你好了
You want the car? Here, take it.
我希望自己从没见过那车
I hope I never see it again.
你在说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
告诉你吧  她就在里面哪
Okay, she's in it.
谁在里面
Who is?
那老太太啊
The old lady.
她可没去天堂  那家伙只挪到后座上去了
She did not go to heaven. She just went to the back seat.
当真
Really?
你说那老太太在你车上闹鬼啊
You're saying the old lady's ghost is haunting your car?
不是  她是在你的车上闹鬼呢
No, she's haunting your car.
怎么回事
What happened?
我刚正开着车呢
I was just driving.
收音机自己就开了
And the radio goes on all by itself...
放着古典音乐  我平时根本不听的那种
Classical music. I don't listen to that.
然后我又闻到香水味
Then I smell perfume...
老太太用的那种香水  我也根本不可能用的
Old lady perfume. I don't wear that.
你疯了吧
You're crazy.
老爸  告诉他说这世上没鬼的
Dad, will you please tell him there's no such thing as ghosts?
我希望可以说啊  盖比
I wish I could, Gabe.
我倒真希望没有啊
I wish I could.
难不成你也相信有鬼的吗
You believe in ghosts too?
我以前也不相信的
Well, I didn't used to.
直到我去了冯塔纳那栋屋子
And then came the fontana house.
我告诉你啊
I'm telling you,
本来只是例行的检查
It seemed like a routine extermination...
阁楼上有一个黑寡妇蜘蛛的窝
A black widow nest up in the attic.
可最后那寡妇
But the widow.
变成了冯塔纳太太
Turned out to be Mrs. Fontana...
是最后的冯塔纳太太本人
The late Mrs. Fontana.
最后就是说已经死了
"Late" Means "Dead."
你们只是想吓唬我罢了
You guys are just trying to scare me.
我倒希望只是吓人  盖比  我希望只是吓人啊
I wish we were, Gabe. I wish we were.
你为什么每句话都要说2遍呢
Why are you saying everything twice?
我不知道  盖比
I don't know, Gabe.
不知道啊
I don't know.
好啦  够啦  我才不相信鬼呢
All right, enough. I don't believe in ghosts.
那车根本没闹鬼  谢谢你的钥匙
That car is not haunted. And thank you.
可别说我没警告你哦
Don't say you weren't warned.
记住  上了那车后
And remember, if you go in that car,
要小心古典音乐  难闻的香水味
Beware of classical music, smelly perfume...
还有谋杀
And murder.
老爸  又没人在车上被谋杀
Dad, nobody was murdered in that car.
现在还没有
Not yet.
别动  我遭遇感情危机了
Don't move. I'm in a relationship crisis.
今天你够走运的  我根本动不起来
This is your lucky day. I rarely move.
斯宾塞
Spencer.
泰迪
Teddy.
怎么搞的  你是不是在一脚踏两船
What's going on? Are you cheating on me?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我看见你搂着一姑娘
I saw you with your arm around that girl.
你在给我搞外遇  是不是啊
You're cheating on me, aren't you?
大家注意了
Attention, everybody.
这个泡果汁的伙计是个花心骗子
Juice boy here is a cheater.
而且他给我的杯子从来倒不满
And he never gives me a full serving either.
泰迪  你完全误会了
Teddy, you've got it all wrong.
哦  是吗  那你是不是经常把胳膊搭在
Oh, okay, so you just put your arm around.
每个顾客的肩上啊  是不是
All your customers, is that it?
不是啊  我只是放在我表妹的肩上而已啦
No, I put my arm around my cousin.
你说什么
Your what?
我的表妹斯凯勒呀
My cousin Skyler.
这样啊
Oh.
原来是你的表妹
Your cousin Skyler.
她看上去人不错呀
She seems nice.
乡亲们  没事了
It's okay, everybody.
那只不过是她的表妹
She's just his cousin.
喝你们的果汁去吧
So return to your juices.
你看  我的休息时间过了  你还是走吧
Look, my break's over. Maybe you should go.
好的  我很抱歉
Yeah, sure. I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
是另外一个小子没给我倒满
It's the other kid who never fills it up.
我自己的车啊
My own car.
广阔的大路啊
The open road,
自由啊  风吹着我的头发
Freedom, wind in my hair,
还有6年就到啦
And it's all just six years away.
香水  不是吧
Perfume? No way.
很不赖嘛  PJ
Very funny, P.J.
PJ  PJ
P.J.? P.J.?
滚出我的车
Get out of my car.
Get out of my car,
小男孩
Little boy.
是谁在说话呀
Who said that?
不然你就留下来陪我吧
Or you can stay with me
永远永远永远陪着我
Forever and ever and ever!
妈妈  妈妈
Mommy! Mommy!
呼
Whew.
很顺利嘛
That went well.
拿去  拿走你这该死的车
Here, take your stupid car!
嗨  你是斯凯勒吧  我是泰迪
Hi. You're Skyler, right? I'm Teddy.
啊  对  我在斯宾塞的钱夹里看到你的照片
Oh, right. I saw your picture in Spencer's wallet.
斯宾塞把我的照片放在他的钱夹里哦
Spencer keeps my picture in his wallet?
真贴心
That's sweet.
当然了  其实是我自己放的
Of course I put it in there,
不过他没把那扔掉真是好贴心
But it's so sweet he didn't throw it out.
你拿了什么来啊
What have you got there?
棍子顶个派
Pie on a stick.
从哪里买的啊
Where did you get it?
那店名就叫"棍子顶个派"
Pie on a stick.
这是我来跟斯宾塞道歉的礼物
It's just my way to say "I'm sorry" To Spencer.
因为之前我有点小题大作
Because I kind of freaked out earlier.
我不知道你俩是表兄妹呢
I didn't know you two were cousins.
我以为你们俩才是表兄妹
I thought you two were cousins.
不是呀  斯宾塞是我的男朋友
No, Spencer's my boyfriend.
不对  斯宾塞是我的男友才是真
啊哦
Uh-oh.
看来你们俩遇到啦
So you two have met, huh?
对呀  还发现大家是表亲呢
Yeah, turns out we're cousins.
你还有什么可说的  斯宾塞
Anything you want to say, Spencer?
要免费试吃不
A free sample?
当然好  给我来点儿
Sure, I'd love one.
嗯  很好喝
Mm, delicious.
你自己也该尝尝这滋味
You should try some.
别忘了还要吃点心
Don't forget dessert.
喂  等等啊
Hey, wait.
你怎么做的出
How could you?
对不起  我可以解释
I'm sorry. I can exp...
别说了
Just don't.
泰迪宝贝  你还好吗
Teddy honey, are you okay?
不好呀
No.
挪过去些
Scoot over.
你看  我知道这样说也许并不能让你好过
Look, I know this probably won't make you feel better,
<i>我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过</i>
But I know what you're going through.
那你也曾这样心碎过吗
So you had your heart broken too?
我有过呀  被兔草德狠狠伤过
I did. By Warren snodgrass.
养兔场的草  什么怪名字啊
Warren snodgrass?
哦  他本人比他名字听上去要可爱的多
Yeah, he was a lot cuter than he sounds.
话说回来  我那时真是疯狂爱着他
Anyway, I was madly in love with him.
接着有一天突然措手不及的
And then one day out of the blue.
他为了金·布鲁克斯而甩了我
He dumped me for Kim Brooks.
我真是太伤心了
I was devastated.
那你最后怎么挺住的
So how did you deal with it?
我没挺住呀
I didn't.
那时我也弄的一团糟  想着我的人生算是完了
I was a mess, thought my life was over.
可后来我还是又开始约会了
But then I started dating.
和那个高个儿的金发傻缺叫大包的好上了
This tall, blond goof ball named Bob.
老爸吗
Dad?
不是  是大包·波克酒
No, Bob diddlebock.
不过是他介绍我认识了你爸
But he introduced me to dad.
听着  宝贝  重点就是
Look, honey, the point is.
如果我没有那时的心碎
If I hadn't had my heart broken,
就不会遇见你们的父亲了
I never would have met your father.
那我也就不会出生了
Then I would have never been born.
现在也就不会这么伤心了
And I wouldn't be so sad right now.
哦  别别  宝贝
Oh, no no, honey.
啊  是很难受  我知道的
Oh, it's terrible, I know.
简直糟透了
It stinks.
可是你知道吗  宝贝
But you know what, babe?
我保证一切都会好的
It will get better. I promise.
小查莉啊  我在这陪着你的姐姐呢
Hi, Charlie. I'm here with your sister.
她第一次失恋啦
Who's having her first broken heart.
第一次而已
My first?
难道以后还会再有啊
There's gonna be more?
不不  宝贝  不会有了
No, honey, this is it.
不管如何  等到你看到这段的时候
Anyway, by the time you're watching this,
你也许也在经历自己的第一次心碎时刻
You might be experiencing your first heartbreak.
所以只要记住  未来终将美好
So just remember, it always gets better.
我只想告诉你
And I just wanted to say.
你对斯宾塞的感觉是正确的
You were right about Spencer.
真糟糕你没有这样一个小妹妹
It's too bad you won't have a little sister.
可以等你到了我这年纪时在旁照看你
Looking out for you when you're my age,
尽管我们还不晓得呢(妈妈也许会再生)
Although we never know.
绝对不会有了啦
Oh, we know.
祝你好运啰  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
什么啊
What the...?
对不起啊
I'm sorry.
放过我吧
Leave me alone.
不要啊
No.
No-o-o!
你真是最棒的小妹妹
You such a good sister.
过来亲一个  mua
Come here. Come here